===============OP=================
===============ED=================
That's you, isn't it, Big Brother?
It's me, Nunnally!
お兄様なのでしょう
私です　ナナリーです
If your memories really haven't returned,
you shouldn't recognize Nunnally.
本当に記憶が戻っていないのなら
ナナリーのことは分からないはず
Go on, Lelouch. Answer her!
さあ　ルルーシュ
答えを出してもらおう
Suzaku...
You've really gone and done it!
スザク　やってくれたな
Um... Is this not my big brother?
あの　お兄様ではないのですか
ダメだ　ナナリーにうそはつけない
It's no use!
I can't lie to Nunnally!
オレは…オレは…
I... I!!!
Rolo?
ロロ？！
Good work! Keep it going!
よくやった　そのまま頼む
Don't forget about the time limit.
時間制限を忘れないで
I understand!
Nunnally, listen to me!
分かっている
聞いてくれ　ナナリー
Big Brother! I knew it!
お兄様　やっぱり
I have to act like we're
strangers right now!
今は他人の振りをしなければならない
It's necessary!
Just follow my lead!
必要なんだ
オレに話を合わせてほしい
I swear, I'll come and get you!
I swear it! So, until then...
必ず迎えに行く
必ず！
だから　それまで
Until then...
それまで…
I love you, Nunnally!
愛してる　ナナリー
Um, I'm afraid you have me
confused with someone else.
あの　人違いではないかと
That's right,
I'm just an ordinary student.
はい　ただの学生ですし
ルルーシュ　やはり記憶は戻っていないのか
Lelouch... Have your memories
really not come back?
Yes. I beg your pardon.
はい　すみません
Forgive me. When I heard it
was a good friend of Suzaku's,
こちらこそ
スザクさんの大切な友達と聞いていたので早とちりしてしまって
I just jumped to conclusions.
It's just... I...
あの　私…
No, please. It's an honor to
speak with a royal princess!
いえ　皇女殿下とお話できて光栄です
Um, could you please put Suzaku back on?
あ　あの　電話を戻してもらえますか
Yes, Your Highness.
イエス　ユア　ハイネス
Forgive me, Nunnally. I didn't mean
to cause a misunderstanding.
ごめん　ナナリー　誤解させるような形になっちゃって
No, it's all right. He just seemed so
similar to him that it surprised me.
いえ　雰囲気が似ていたので驚いてしまって
Holy Britannian Empire
CALIFORNIA BASE
あの　では　エリア11でお会いしましょう
侮ってはなりません
Well, um... I'll see you when I get to Area 11.
Don't make light of this. Whatever his
disadvantages are, we're dealing with Zero!
どれだけ不利であろうと　ゼロのことです
He's sure to have some
scheme in the works!
必ず　何か仕掛けてきます
Such timid words!
Not what I'd expect...
弱気だな
それでも「帝国の先槍」と呼ばれた男か
from the man called the
Spearhead of the Empire!
Viceroy Nunnally shall have me with her.
There will be no need for you.
ナナリー総督には私がついている
貴公の出番などない
But, what about Zero?
しかし　ゼロは…
Lord Guilford!
ギルフォード卿
Zero is already dead! The Zero we face
now has just appropriated his name!
ゼロは　すでに死んでいる
今のゼロは　その名を　かたっているだけ
Don't you think Princess Cornelia would
find your fear of an impostor inexcusable?!
偽者におびえるなど
コーネリア皇女殿下に申し訳ないとは思わんのか
Excuuuse me!
申し訳ない
Earl Lloyd!
ロイド伯爵？
ランスロットのユニット調整に手間取ってねぇ
Adjusting the Lancelot's unit took
a long time! Sorry we're late.
遅刻しちゃいました
It's been a while, Dr. Lloyd.
お久しぶりです　ロイド博士
No prob! We've been under
Charlie's direct service, after all.
いや～　皇帝ちゃんの直属になったから
How DARE you refer to his
Imperial Majesty in such a way!
不敬であろう　皇帝陛下に対して
F- Forgive him, sir! Lloyd!
も…申し訳ありません
ロイドさん
ん？何かまずかったっけ
Did I say something wrong?
I see you haven't changed.
So, as for that item?
相変わらずですね
で　例の物ですが…
Yes. It came via
Prince Schneizel's line.
はい　シュナイゼル殿下のラインから
Nice, having the
second prince to call.
もつべきものは　第2皇子様だね
I appreciate it.
助かります
For heaven's sake!
まったく
With this good-for-nothing nobleman
working as Sir Kururugi's guardian,
枢木卿の後見人をこんな放蕩貴族が勤めているとは
his wantonness will just
rub off on the new viceroy!
新総督の教育上も喜ばしくはないな
I was wondering if
Suzaku has been lying to me.
スザクさんはうそをついているのかしら
でも　お兄様だって…
But now Big Brother, too?
Has something happened
between them?
お二人の間に　何が
Asa mo yoru mo koikogarete
Morning and night, I long for you
朝も夜も恋い焦がれて
星になるよ 君守る
hoshi ni naru yo kimi mamoru
I'll become a star and protect you
tatakai wa yukue shirazu
No matter where the battle may take me
戦いは行方知らず
ashita to kinou no kousaten de
At the intersection of tomorrow and yesterday
明日と昨日の交差点で
majiwaranai kimi to boku
You and I can't be together
交わらない君と僕
ima iku yo boku wa nagareboshi
I'm a shooting star, on my way right now
今行くよ 僕は流れ星
sekai ga kuchihatetemo
Even if the world crumbles apart
世界が朽ち果てても 変わることの無いものがある
kawaru koto no nai mono ga aru
There are things which will never change
namida wo koraete demo
Even as we bear tears in our eyes
涙を堪えてでも 守るべきものが僕らにはある
mamorubeki mono ga bokura ni wa aru
There are things we must protect
nanman'nen nan'okunen mae kara no
A message that's been in my body
（nononono）
遅れまいと メッセージが絶えない
message ga tainai de
For thousands and millions of years,
（no）
uzukidasu... mayoi wa nai
Springs out... I have no reservations
剥き出す 撃ち抜く
（迷いは無い）
narihibiku... kantan da
Roars out... It's easy
（簡単だ）
shagareta koe de... asu wo yobu
In a hoarse voice... Calling tomorrow
しゃがれた声で 傷だらけの手で 君守る
kizudarake no te de... kimi mamoru
With my wounded hands... I protect you
way got you could like
I continue to fight...
I continue to fight!
asa mo yoru mo koikogarete
Morning and night, I long for you
朝も夜も恋い焦がれて
hoshi ni naru yo kimi mamoru
I'll become a star and protect you
星になるよ 君守る
戦いは行方知らず
tatakai wa yukue shirazu
No matter where the battle may take me
ashita to kinou no kousaten de
At the intersection of tomorrow and yesterday
明日と昨日の交差点で
majiwaranai kimi to boku
You and I can't be together
交わらない君と僕
sadame wo kirisaku nagareboshi
I'm a shooting star, tearing fate apart
宿命を切り裂く流れ星
afureru kimi no namida boku ga ima ubaisaru
I'll take away your overflowing tears right now
溢れる君の涙 僕が今奪い去る
SURPRISE ATTACK OVER THE PACIFIC
新総督は予定どおり明日このエリア11に赴任されます
The new viceroy is set to arrive here in
Area 11 tomorrow to take up her new post.
The name and personal history of the
new viceroy has yet to be released.
新しい総督の名前や経歴は依然伏せられたままで
The big question in all this is the
Chinese Federation consulate.
問題は中華連邦の総領事館でしょう
ゼロの件ですね
In regard to Zero, you mean?
公式発表がないため
As there has been
no formal announcement,
高亥総領事の独断ではないかという声もあります
some are questioning whether Consul
General Gao Hai is acting on his own.
総領事の国内での立場はパワーバランスの…
The consul general's domestic standing
is caught in the power balance of...
Chinese Federation Capital City - LUOYANG -
エリア11の情勢は
さあ　詳しいことは私も
How go things in Area 11?
I'm not sure. Even I don't know all the details.
外の世界はどうなっているのですか
What goes on in the outside world?
I've never set foot outside of this palace.
私はこの城から出たことがないから
天子様　この洛陽が朱禁城こそ世界の中心ですよ
Your Majesty, Luoyang...
Indeed, the Vermilion Forbidden City itself,
is the center of the entire world!
でも…
But...
では　私が　外を見てまいります
Well then, I shall go out
and see what is happening.
実は　今日はお暇を告げにまいりましたの
The truth is,
I came today to say goodbye.
そんな
Oh, no! Not after you and I
have become friends!
せっかく　初めてお友達ができたのに
申し訳ありません
I beg your pardon,
but my husband is waiting for me.
でも　夫が待っておりますので
Receipt of the supplies in Niigata
was apparently successful.
ニイガタでの物資受け取りはうまくいったらしい
そうか
I see.
しかし　この総領事館に戻る方法がないが
However, there's no way for them
to return here to the consulate.
だろうな
As I'd expect.
新しい総督が　ナナリー
The new viceroy
is going to be Nunnally.
戦えるのか　妹と
Will you be able to fight her?
Your own sister?
戦う？ナナリーと？
Fight? With Nunnally?
What sort of joke is that?
それは何の冗談だ
では　ほうっておくのか
Then you're going
to leave her alone?
論外だな
Out of the question.
このままでは　昔のように
If nothing is done, Nunnally will be used
as a political tool, like we used to be!
ナナリーがまた政治の道具に
歩けず　目も不自由な少女
A blind, crippled young girl...
駒として使い捨てるつもりかな
Do they plan to use her as a
pawn and then throw her away?
くっ　そうさせないためにオレは行動を起こした
I'm doing all this to keep
that from happening!
そのための黒の騎士団だ
That's why I formed
the Black Knights!
ナナリーのためのゼロなんだ
I became Zero for Nunnally's sake!
それがお前の生きる理由であることは知っている
I know that is your reason
for living. However...
しかし…
オレはナナリーが幸せに過ごせる世界をつくる
I am going to create a world in
which Nunnally can live happily!
そのためにもブリタニアを破壊する
And for that, I will destroy
Britannia as well!
V.V.とかいうヤツはブリタニア本国にいるのか
Is that V.V. person you mentioned
in the Britannian homeland?
そこまでは分からない
I don't know that much.
しかしV.V.はお前の父ブリタニア皇帝　シャルルの最初の同志
However, I do know that he was
the first comrade your father,
Emperor Charles of
Britannia, ever knew.
同志？
"Comrade?"
かつて　二人は誓った
Once, they made a
vow to each other.
神を殺す
God shall die!
That is our contract.
それが僕らの契約
ねぇ　シャルル
Tell me, Charles,
why did you not tell Nunnally?
どうしてナナリーには教えなかったの
ゼロの正体とギアすのことを
About Zero's true identity.
And about Geass.
その必要はないでしょう
It wasn't necessary
for her to know.
シャルル　君は　まだ幼いね
Charles...
You're still such a child.
そうですかねぇ　兄さん
I suppose I am... big brother.
ナナリー総督は？
Where is Viceroy Nunnally?
庭園にいます
In the garden.
Even if she came to the bridge...
ブリッジに来られても…
It'd make no difference.
ふっ　意味はないな
Area 11 - TOKYO SETTLEMENT
いない　黒の騎士団が？
ああ　我々も先程確認したばかりだ
They're not here?! The Black Knights?!
Yes. We only just confirmed it ourselves. You know as much about it as we do.
情報は共有しよう
これで我が国には　ブリタニアに対する敵意はないと分かっていただけるかな
Now you should see that my country has
no hostile intentions against Britannia.
ゼロも一緒に？
And Zero went with them?!
そのようだ
It appears so. They vanished
along with their Knightmares.
ナイトメアごといなくなっているしな
地下の階層から立ち去ったようだ
It looks like they left
via an underground level.
くっ　どこへ
To where?
さあ　そこまでは
Who knows?
That's all I have.
They wouldn't!
Attack Nunnally?!
まさか…ナナリーを
やられたな
We've been had.
お返しする
Shall we... pay them back?
黒の騎士団
The Black Knights!
作戦目的は　新総督を捕虜とすることにある
The objective of this operation is
the capture of the new viceroy!
いかなることがあろうと　絶対に傷をつけるな
No matter what happens,
she absolutely must not be harmed!
いいな　絶対にだ
Is that clear?!
Absolutely no harm!
承知
Wilco!
What are you doing, Tamaki?!
何やってんだ　玉城
素人め　陸戦兵器を空に上げても
Amateurs! Even if you bring those ground
combat units into the sky, you won't...
サーフェイスフレアを張られても問題はない
Even deploying surface flares
won't matter to us! Surround them!
囲んでたたけ
藤堂将軍　あとは頼みます
General Tohdoh,
the rest is up to you.
ああ　副司令たちも　無事でな
Right. Good luck to
your people, Deputy-Commander.
まさか　この上に？
Impossible!
They're landing on top of us?!
敵性ナイトメア更に2機本艦主翼上に取り付きました
Two enemy Knightmares have
already landed on our main wing!
護衛艦にも取りついたようです
They're on our escorts as well!
Send our air forces to...
航空戦力を…
愚かな指揮官め
You fool of a commander...
航空戦力をスモークに集中させることぐらい
I already anticipated that you'd
concentrate your air power on the smoke.
すでに読んでいた
旗艦以外は用なしだよ
The flagship's all we're after.
よし　我々は離脱する
All right!
We're withdrawing!
残った空戦部隊も出せ
Send out our remaining
air combat units!
護衛艦からも　砲撃を
Have our escort ships
open fire as well!
しかし　敵がフロートを狙っています
But sir, the enemy
are targeting our float units!
シールドを展開しているため照準が…
We can't target them because
we have our shields deployed!
ここを守らずしてどうする
And what are we supposed to do
if we can't defend this ship?!
くっ　こんなことならギルフォード卿も連れてくるべきだったな
If I'd known this would happen,
I would have brought Lord Guilford with us!
トウキョウ租界から援軍が来るとしても　約1時間
It'll take at least an hour before reinforcements
from the Tokyo settlement reach us!
ナイトメアが　中に入ってきたら
What if the enemy
Knightmares get inside?
墜落だな
Then we crash. Anyway, our job
right now is to help any survivors.
それより　こっちは生存者を
Wha? Is that?
えっ　まさか…
死ね
Die!
分かった
Sure.
Understood, sir.
Nunnally...
I'm coming to save you.
ナナリー今助けに行くから
秘技　八艘飛びってね
My secret technique...
The surprise leap
between floating ships!
シールドを展開してもその中に入っちゃえば　こっちのものさ
You may have your shields buttoned up,
but they're useless if we get inside!
航空戦力もおしまいみたいだし
Looks like their air forces
are finished, too.
Don't let arrogance be your downfall.
浮かれていると因幡の白兎になるぞ
はいはい　基本に忠実に
Right, right.
I'll stick to the fundamentals.
トウキョウからの援軍　早すぎる
Reinforcements from Tokyo?
But it's too soon!
いや　方角としては　後ろ備え
No, it looks like
their rear guard.
それに　フロートユニット？
Besides that...
They have float units?
ナイトメア？
Knightmares!
そんな　あの機体は…
It can't be...
That machine is!
さあ　幕を下ろそう
Now then... Let us bring down
the curtain on this.
全機　出力正常です
Output on all units is nominal.
量産は愉快だねぇ
Don't you love the marvel
of mass-production?
本当によかったんですか
Are you really okay with this?
You charged the expense to Prince Schneizel.
経費をシュナイゼル殿下に
いいんじゃない　そのうち　気づくだろうし
So what?
He hasn't noticed yet.
えっ？話してなかったんですか
What?!
You mean you didn't tell him first?!
空が飛べなくたって
Even if we can't fly!
勘は悪くない
You have good instincts...
But your machine's outclassed!
だが　機体特性は…
すまん　あとは
Sorry! See you later!
ギルフォードめ　勝手なことを
Damn your impudence, Guilford!
But we're saved, My Lord!
しかし　助かりました
それは　ヤツの手柄ということだ
For which he will get all the credit!
条件はすでにクリアされた
All conditions
have been cleared.
これで　戦局は逆転する
And now, the tide of
battle shall be turned!
ナ…ナナリー
N- Nunnally...
おい　ゼロが艦内に
Hey! Zero's inside the ship!
What are those guards doing?!
ガードは何をしている
ナナリー総督　ゼロです
Viceroy Nunnally, it's Zero!
今　アプソン将軍に
I'm informing
General Upson right now...
二人の出会いを妨げてはならない
Their reunion must
not be disturbed.
N- Nunnally...
ナ　ナナリー
At last, we're together again.
At last...
やっと　会えた
やっと…
That's you there, Zero, isn't it?
Have you come to kill me as well?
そこにいるのは　ゼロなのですね
私も殺すのですか
クロヴィス兄様やユフィ姉様のように
Like you did my brother
Clovis and sister Euphy?
でも　少しだけ待っていただけませんか
Even so, will you wait
just a moment, please?
あなたは　間違っていると思うのです
I think...
I think what you're doing is wrong!
くっ　ハーケンを
His harken!
Kouzuki, now!
今だ　紅月君
はい
Yes, sir!
さあ　お仕置きタイムだ
Okay, it's punishment time!
おかしな戦闘機だね
Weird-looking fighter plane.
Even so!
でもさ…
A Knightmare?!
ナイトメア？
すみません　あとは
Sorry! It's up to you guys, now!
残る敵は4機となりました
That just leaves four enemy units.
ナイトオブラウンズまで？
The Knights of the Round as well?!
I'll never bear this disgrace...
これでは　私の評価が…
どうした？
Now what?!
右翼護衛艦　操舵不能
Starboard escort ship
has lost control!
このままでは　本艦に
It's on a collision course!
進路変更を
Change course!
間に合いません　衝突します
We'll never make it!
We're going to collide!
相変わらずだな
As usual, you have
Mordred do his thing.
モルドレッドのやることは
アーニャ　もうそれは　使うなよ
Anya, don't use that anymore, okay?
We don't want to kill the viceroy, do we?
総督殺しはまずいだろ
守ったのに
After I saved her...
ロイドさん　ランスロットは
Lloyd!
What's the Lancelot's status?!
準備出来てるよ～ん　早くおいで
Ready and waiting for you!
Hurry on over!
将軍　何をなさるおつもりです
General!
What do you think you're doing?!
このままでは　降格となる
At this rate,
I'm going to be demoted!
私自らの手で功績を
I have to perform some
deed by my own hand!
黒の騎士団を…
Destroy the Black Knights!
愚か者　自らのエンジンを
Fool!
You'd shoot your own engines?!
今　私の前にゼロがいる
Zero is standing
in front of me right now.
お兄様　私に勇気をください
Big brother...
Give me the courage I need!
間違っているのはブリタニアだ
It's Britannia who is wrong.
The emperor only values strength.
皇帝は強さこそ絶対の価値と考えている
君もそれに賛同するのか
Do you also approve of that?
それは…
Well...
ナナリー総督　君は利用されているだけなんだよ
Viceroy Nunnally...
You're just being used.
You're saying they sent a blind, crippled girl
to win everyone's sympathy? You're wrong.
目も足も不自由な私なら
みんなの同情を引けると
違います
私は自ら望んだのです
I came because I wanted to.
ゼロとは
What's Zero's status?
ECCMの影響か　連絡が取れん
E.C.C.M. effects are
preventing contact with him.
後方の千葉　紅月と合流し
I want to rendezvous with Chiba and Kouzuki
in the aft section and scout inside the ship.
艦内探索をかけたいが…
しかし　この艦は　墜落しかけています
But this ship's going to crash.
Do you have time...
時間が
Senba!
仙波
弱い者いじめは好きじゃないけどさ
I don't like picking on those
who are weaker than me, but...
こんな　ところで…
Never thought...
it'd be in a place like this!
SENBA!
仙波！
藤堂
Tohdoh! It's not like you to launch an
ambush in ground combat weaponry!
陸戦兵器での奇襲とは　お前らしからぬ戦だな
あなたが望んだ？
You wanted to?
I think I can make the world
a more peaceful and gentle place.
せ　世界はもっと平和に　優しく変えていけると思うんです
だから　私はユフィ姉様の遺志を継ぎ
That's why I'm going to carry on Euphy's will and
recreate the Specially Administrated Zone of Nippon.
もう一度　行政特区日本を…
復活させると？
You're bringing that back?!
ゼロ　あなたも　そこに参加してもらえませんか
Zero... Won't you help me
to make it happen?
If you're human, you'd try it again!
やり直せるはずです　人は
Zero's come to steal
Nunnally away.
ゼロはナナリーを奪いに来た
しかし　機情からの報告はない
But there's been no word from the O.S.I.
敵はゼロか　ルルーシュか
So, am I fighting
Zero or Lelouch?
枢木卿　状況を　確認します
Sir Kururugi, I'm going to
confirm the situation.
ナナリー総督を乗せた機体は
The #2 float unit on the vessel carrying
Viceroy Nunnally has shut down.
2番フロートが停止状態
3番4番フロートに相互連動
The #3 and #4 float units are interlinked,
so a case theta has occurred.
ケース　シータ発生
まあ　早い話が
Long story short,
everyone's going to end up taking a swim.
このままだと　みんなで海水浴ってこと
アプソン将軍が戦死したって報告もあるけど
Except for General Upson,
who's been reported K.I.A.
今は総督の救出を優先します
Right now, rescuing
the viceroy has top priority!
ホイールチェアの信号探索　開始
Initiating search
for her wheelchair beacon.
ECMによるノイズ　クリーニング　スタート
Starting E.C.M.
signal noise cleanup!
フェイズをプリセット
Phase, preset. Transmitting
interior schematic of lead ship.
先行して　艦内配置　送信
データリンク　確認
Data link, confirmed.
Complete.
コンプリート
総督現在位置　確認後　送信願う
Transmit the viceroy's location
as soon as it's confirmed.
チャンネルMB　ラジャー
Channel M.B., roger!
ランスロット·コンクエスター
Lancelot Conquista... take off!
発艦
Taking off!
カレン　僕はナナリーを助けなくちゃいけない
Kallen, I have to save Nunnally.
I won't ask you to forgive me any more!
今更　許しは
請わないよ
隠れろ　紅月
Kouzuki, hide!
Get inside the ship!
艦内に入れば
でも　みんなが　逃げ切るまで
But! Not until everyone's
gotten away!
まさか
Impossible!
紅月！
KOUZUKI!
Pull the ejection lever, Kouzuki!
ええい　脱出レバーを　紅月
ダメ　動かない
No use!
It won't work!
整備不良？こんなときに…
Lousy maintenance?!
Now, of all times!
おしまい　隠れんぼは
Hide and seek is over now.
落ちちゃう
I'm falling! Forgive me, Guren...
ごめんね　紅蓮
お母さん　お兄ちゃん
Mother... Big brother...
ベストポジションじゃない
Well, aren't you
in the best position.
ラクシャータさん？
Wha? Rakshata?
お待たせ　黒の騎士団特製の飛翔滑走翼
Sorry for the wait. I have the Black
Knights' special flight wing pack for you.
You reviewed
the manual I sent, right?
教本の予習はちゃんとやってた
はい　大丈夫です
Uh... Yeah! I'll be fine!
じゃあ　本番いってみようか
All right, then let's
try it out for real!
基本誘導はこちらでやりますね
We'll give you the basic
guidance from here.
ゼロ様の救出を頼みます
Please go and rescue Master Zero.
はい
R- Right!
Opening number 3
vertical launch chamber.
参番垂直発射管　開放
紅蓮弐式本体との接続信号　確認
Connection signal with
Guren Mk-II, confirmed.
舞い上がりな　飛翔滑走翼
Take to the skies, my flight wings!
回れ
Turn around!
誘導信号　確認
Guidance signal, confirmed.
同調軸　測的よし
Alignment angle, nominal.
Link up.
連結
Linking up!
飛べ！
FLY!!!
続けて
Continue! Armor piercing
ordnance right arm unit!
徹甲砲撃右腕部
Right arm unit dropping
speed for linkup.
右腕部　連結速度まで減速中
伝送ニューロン　コンマ5からコンマ8MMP
（MMP：Minimal　Model　Program）
Transmission neuron 0.5 to 0.8 M.M.P.
障害に感なし
No blockage detected.
屈伸筋　第1から第5まで　正常に作動しています
Elastic muscles 1 through 5
are operating normally.
衝撃コントロール　始動を確認
Confirm activation of shock control.
Linking up.
連結できます
カレン　頼む
Kallen, please!
敵がどれだけいようと
No matter what the enemy
throws at me!
Our unit will go after Tohdoh!
我が隊は藤堂を追います
ああ　こっちは総督を…
Right, and we'll
go after the viceroy.
ん　空に？
In the sky? The Black Knights
have float units, too?
黒の騎士団もフロートを？
紅月君　ゼロを…
Kouzuki! Save Zero!
助けてみせます
I'll try, sir!
ほう　空とシールドを手にしたか
Oh? You have both flight
and a shield, eh? Even so...
しかし…
この紅蓮が通用しなかったら　おしまいね
If this new Guren can't
handle them, it's all over!
でも　やるしかないから
Still, you don't have much choice,
so why not try shooting?
撃ってみましょうか
You've got a point, there!
そりゃ　そうですね
え　遠距離で？
F- From long range?!
やれる
I can do it!
With this Guren Flight-Enabled Version!
この紅蓮可翔式なら
Hm...
スザク　お前は総督を
Suzaku, get to the viceroy!
油断するな
Don't let your guard down!
That pilot was able to beat Lord Jeremiah!
相手は　ジェレミア卿に勝ったこともあるパイロットだ
あのオレンジにかよ？
That Orange guy, huh?
この
You!
おいおい　ラウンズ並みの腕前か
Whoa! Is she as good
as the Rounds?
でも　これで…
Still... Let her beat this.
紅蓮をなめるな
Don't underestimate the Guren!
土足で
With its shoes?
あんたらは後回し
I'll take care of you guys later!
更にワイドレンジで？
It can do wide-range, too?!
エネルギー総量は
What's its total energy?!
拡散させただけです
It was just scattered.
しかし　機体ダメージから　しばらくは動けないかと
But she damaged those units enough that
I doubt they'll be able to move for a while.
何　あのナイトメア
Just what is that Knightmare?
いや　パイロットでしょ
No, it's the pilot.
本気だしときゃよかった
I shouldn't have held back.
カレン　この状況で　また来るなんて
Kallen... You're coming back,
in this situation?
まさか　旗艦の中にゼロが？
Could Zero be inside the ship?!
どけ！
OUT OF MY WAY!!!
食らわせな　ゲフィオンネット
Have a taste of the Gefjun Net!
それは　対策済みさ
We have a countermeasure for this!
Even so, you're still
stuck where you are!
でも　足は止まったね
そんな
Impossible! I thought they
upgraded my Yggdrasil Drive!
ユグドラシルドライブのパワーも上がっているはずなのに
スザク君
Suzaku!
総督の現在位置が分かったわ
We've located the viceroy! She's in the
garden space to the rear of the main bridge!
メインブリッジ後方のガーデンスペース
でも　墜落まで　あと47秒
But you only have
47 seconds till the ship crashes!
必ず助けます
I promise, I'll save her!
Damn!
しまった
うぎゃ
カレン　今はスザクより
Kallen!
Forget about Suzaku!
ゼロ様を
Save Master Zero!
I know, but where is he?!
分かってるけど　どこに
もう時間がない
There's no time left. I'll have to
use the Core Luminous Cone.
コアルミナスコーンを使って
ゴー
Go!
どうすればいい
What do I do?
I can't reveal Zero's true identity to her.
ゼロの正体を明かすわけには
しかし　強引に連れていくのは
But taking her by force
may end up twisting her mind!
ナナリーの意志をねじ曲げることに
スザク
Suzaku!
逃げるぞ　オレと
Escape with me!
ナナリー
Nunnally!
スザクさん！
SUZAKU!!!
違う　そいつは　オレを皇帝に売り払った
No! He's the one who
sold me out to the emperor!
スザクさん
Suzaku!
Were you afraid?
Forgive me! It's all right now!
怖かったかい　ごめん
もう大丈夫だから
Nunnally... With Suzaku!
ナナリーが…
スザクと…
Zero! Right now...
ゼロ　今は
NUNNALLY!!!
ナナリー！
胸の中 いつか拾った
Mune no naka itsuka hirotta
Someday let's try to pick up and rebuild
幸せの欠片 集めてみよう
Shiawase no kakera atsumete miyou
The fragments of happiness in our hearts
忘れかけていたメロディー
Wasurekaketeita melody
That nearly forgotten melody
色褪せず僕の真ん中に
Iroasezu boku no man'naka ni
Stay vivid, deep inside of me
ありがとう 心から 僕に今があるのはみんなのおかげさ
Arigatou kokoro kara
I thank you from the bottom of my heart
Boku ni ima ga aru no wa minna no okagesa
Everything I have now, I owe to everyone
ありがとう 心から 次は僕がみんなにハッピー贈るよ
Arigatou kokoro kara
I thank you from the bottom of my heart
Tsugi wa boku ga minna ni happy okuru yo
Next I'll send happiness to everyone
何もかも忘れないよ あの日の僕も僕だから
Nanimokamo wasurenai yo
I won't forget anything
Ano hi no boku mo boku dakara
Because I'm still the same as I was that day
「大好きだよ」って　いつも言ってあげなきゃ駄目だね
Daisuki da yo'tte itsumo
You need me to keep on saying
Itte agenakya dame da ne
How much I love you
涙がこぼれそうな長い夜は ふっと振り返って
Namida ga kobore sou na nagai yoru wa
On those long nights, your tears about to overflow
Futto furikaette
Just turn around
足跡を辿るんだ あの日を忘れないように
Ashiato wo tadorun'da
Follow those footprints
Ano hi wo wasurenai you ni
So that you'll never forget that day
Ever since my mother
was killed eight years ago,
ナナリーにも夢はある
ナナリーにも選ぶべき道はある
ever since I was
abandoned by Britannia,
とても当たり前で
protecting Nunnally has
meant everything to me.
とても簡単なことなんだよな
Taking care of her room,
preparing her food, everything.
ああ　オレは…
But... I was a fool!
Nunnally has dreams of her own.
There is a path Nunnally
has chosen for herself.
That fact is so obvious.
It's so simple.
Yes... I must!
THE ABANDONED MASK